IBT0052
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
IBT Local 682 records
1950-1960
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
IBT0052
1 Linear Feet
Arrangement
Organized into 2 series: Local 366 and Local 682
- Local 366, Series 1
  - Amalgamated Association of Laundry and Cleaning Companies, 1945-1949; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - St. Louis Cleaners: Wage Agreements, 1946-1947; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - St. Louis Cleaners: Contracts [1], 1947; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - St. Louis Cleaners: Contracts [2], January 1948; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - St. Louis Cleaners: Contracts [3], February-November 1948; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - St. Louis Cleaners: Contracts [4], September 1948; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - St. Louis Cleaners: Contracts [5], 1949; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - St. Louis Cleaners: Contracts [6], March 1950-1951; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - St. Louis Cleaners: Contracts [7], July 1950; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - St. Louis Cleaners: Contracts [8], July 1950; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - St. Louis Dry Cleaners Exchange, 1937-1952; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - St. Louis Linens: Contracts [1], 1947-1948; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - St. Louis Linens: Contracts [2], 1948-1949; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - St. Louis Linens: Contracts [3], 1951-1953; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - William Frenger papers, 1937-1960; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Local 682, Series 2
  - AGC-St. Louis: Contracts, 1960-1962; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - AGC-St. Louis: Correspondence [1], 1963; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - AGC-St. Louis: Correspondence [2], 1964; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - AGC-St. Louis: Correspondence [3], 1965; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Miscellanous, 1957-1962; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Non-Discrimination in Employment Contracts, 1962-1965; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Roster of Local 682 members, Undated; Series 2 (Box SHARED box 33, Folder 3)